shophq.com 2018-03-04

# Evine | Be Good to Yourself | Shop online. Anywhere. Anytime.

**Effective February 1, 2017**

**Scope of this Online Privacy Statement**

This Online Privacy Statement describes how Evine uses, shares and protects the personal information we collect through EVINE.com ("EVINE.com" or "this site"). EVINE.com includes EVINE.tv, which may be accessed via links on EVINE.com or directly at http://TV.EVINE.com and Evine Mobile Applications. "Personal information" is information that identifies you personally, either alone or in combination with other information. Personal information may include, for example, your name, address, email address, credit card information, and transaction history. This Online Privacy Statement is part of and incorporated into the EVINE.com [Terms of Use](http://www.evine.com/p/help/evine/terms-of-use/).

**Your Consent to This Online Privacy Statement**

By browsing or using EVINE.com, you are agreeing to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Online Privacy Statement. If you do not consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Online Privacy Statement, you should not use this site. This Online Privacy Statement may change from time to time (see below). Your continued use of this site after we make changes is deemed acceptance of this changes, so please check the site periodically for updates.

**Questions Concerning Our Online Privacy Practices**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Online Privacy Statement or our privacy practices, please email us or write to us at Evine, 6740 Shady Oak Road, Eden Prairie, Minnesota 55344.

**Privacy Notices**

This Online Privacy Statement may be supplemented or amended from time to time by "privacy notices" posted on this site. For example, certain pages of this site contain privacy notices providing details about the ways we use or share the personal information we collect on those pages.

**This Online Privacy Statement May Change**

We reserve the right to update or modify this Online Privacy Statement, at any time and without prior notice, by posting the revised version on this site. These changes will only apply to personal information we collect after we have posted the revised Online Privacy Statement on this site. Your use of this site following any such change constitutes your agreement that all personal information collected from or about you through EVINE.com after the revised Online Privacy Statement is posted will be subject to the terms of the revised Online Privacy Statement.

The date the Online Privacy Statement was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up to date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our site and this Online Privacy Statement to check for any changes. You may access the current version of this Online Privacy Statement at any time by clicking on the link marked "Privacy Statement" at the bottom of each page of this site.

**What Personal Information Do We Collect on Evine.com?**

**Information You Give Us**

We collect the personal information you knowingly and voluntarily provide when you use EVINE.com, for example, the information you provide when you register, sign-in, search, purchase products, apply for credit, participate in a contest or questionnaire, submit product reviews, sign up for our e-mails, or communicate with customer service. Depending on how you use this site, you may supply us with information such as your name, address, phone number, email address, credit card information, browse history, or information about people to whom purchases will be shipped (for example, a gift recipient).

**Information Sent to Us by Your Web Browser**

We collect information that is sent to us by your Web browser, including but not limited to your IP address, the address of the Web page you were visiting when you accessed EVINE.com, the date and time of your visit, and information about your computer's operating system or mobile device. Please check your browser or mobile device if you want to learn what information your browser or mobile device sends or how to change your settings. The information provided by your browser or mobile device does not identify you personally. We use this non-personal information primarily to create statistics that help us improve this site and make it more compatible with the technology used by our visitors. However, if you have created a user identity on one of your visits to this site or if you access this site by clicking on a link in an email we have sent you, we may combine the information provided by your browser to information that identifies you personally.

**Information We Collect Using Cookies and Other Web Technologies**

We use "cookies" and other Web technologies to collect information and support certain features of this site. For example, we use these technologies to collect information about the ways visitors use our site – which pages they visit, which links they use, and how long they stay on each page. Cookies and other Web technologies are also used to support the features and functionality of our site — for example, to track the contents of your shopping cart as you move from page to page. These technologies also permit us to keep a record of your previous choices and preferences so that we can personalize your shopping experience and save you the trouble of reentering information already in our database. Generally, the information we collect using these Web technologies does not identify you personally, however, it may be linked to information that does identify you personally, such as the information you provide when you make a purchase or register to use a special feature of this site. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you may set your browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer. You may also delete our cookies as soon as you leave EVINE.com. Although you are not required to accept our cookies when you visit EVINE.com, if you set your browser to reject cookies, you will not be able to use all of the features and functionality of this site.

**Information We Collect From Other Sources**

We may supplement the information collected through this site with information we collect in other ways. For example, if you call our toll-free number, we may collect your telephone number and add it to our database. We may also supplement the information collected through this site with information from third parties, including data brokers. By supplementing your profile with information from other sources, we are better able to provide product recommendations and special offers that will be of genuine interest to you. We may also use this additional information to further personalize our site and improve your shopping experience.

**Use of Cookies and Similar Technologies by Our Advertising Agents**

Evine uses third-party advertising companies to place online advertisements on our behalf at websites other than EVINE.com. These advertising companies may use cookies and Web beacons (also known as "pixel tags") to target and measure the effectiveness of their advertisements. For example, our advertising companies may place Web beacons on their clients' websites. When you visit these websites, the Web beacon "tags" your computer with a "cookie" that collects and stores information about your visit to their client's websites. This information does not identify you personally. Our advertising companies use the information they collect about your use of their clients' Web sites to customize the advertisements you see when you visit their clients' websites. Our advertising companies' use of cookies and Web beacons is covered by their privacy policies, not by this Online Privacy Statement.

**How Do We Use Your Personal Information?**

We may use the personal information we collect through Evine.com

  * to fulfill your order for Evine products or services;
  * to provide you with the information, products and services you request or purchase;
  * for security, credit or fraud prevention purposes;
  * to register your purchase with the manufacturer or service provider for warranty or similar purposes;
  * to provide you with effective customer service;
  * to provide you with a personalized shopping experience;
  * to display personalized advertising when you visit this site;
  * to contact you with special offers and other information we believe will be of interest to you;
  * to contact you with information and notices related to your use of this site or your purchases;
  * to invite you to participate in surveys and provide feedback to us;
  * to better understand the your needs and interests;
  * to improve the content, functionality and usability of this site;
  * to improve the content, functionality and usability of our Mobile Applications;
  * to improve our products and services;
  * to improve our marketing and promotional efforts; and
  * for any other purpose we identify in a specific privacy notice.

**With Whom Do We Share the Personal Information We Collect Through Evine.com?**

We may share the personal information we collect through this site as described below and in any applicable privacy notices.

**Our Corporate Affiliates**

We may share your personal information with our subsidiaries and parent and sister corporations (our "corporate affiliates"), who may use this information to contact you with information and offers they believe will be of interest to you. The corporate affiliates' use of your personal information shall be subject to this Online Privacy Statement.

**Our Service Providers**

We may share your personal information with companies that perform services on our behalf. Our service providers are required by contract to protect the confidentiality of the personal information we share with them and to use it only to provide services on our behalf.

**Synchrony Bank Credit Card**

All of the personal information we collect in connection with your participation in the Evine Card program, including the information you provide when you apply for a Evine Card is shared with Synchrony Bank (“Synchrony”), the financial institution that issues the Evine Card. Synchrony’s use of this personal information is governed by the Synchrony Privacy Policy and any contracts between you and Synchrony. In addition, if you do not have an Evine Card, we may share the personal information you provide during the checkout process with Synchrony for the limited purpose of giving Synchrony the information they need to determine whether to offer you the opportunity to apply for one of these cards at checkout.

**Extended Warranty Providers and Other Vendors**

If you purchase an extended warranty through EVINE.com, we will share with the company that provides the extended warranty the information they need to service the extended warranty and offer you renewal and other options.

**Other Business Partners and Selected Vendors**

We work closely with certain business partners and carefully selected vendors to provide you with access to their product offerings. We may share personally identifiable information about you with these business partners or selected vendors, and they may use this information to offer you products and/or services that they believe will be of interest to you.

**Business Transfers**

Information submitted to Evine or EVINE.com is an asset of Evine and will become part of our normal business records. Your personal information may be transferred to another company (either a corporate affiliate or an unrelated third party) that has acquired substantially all the stock or assets of Evine, one of our corporate affiliates, or one of our operating divisions, for example, as the result of a sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or liquidation. Evine or EVINE.com shall provide notice of such transfer by sending you an email to the email address in your Evine account settings.

**Government and Legal Disclosures**

We may disclose the personal information we collect through EVINE.com when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law (or a court order or subpoena); to prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; to enforce the Terms of Use or other agreements that govern your use of this site; to protect the rights, property or safety of Evine, our users or others; or to protect your vital interests. If you have purchased products from us on extended payment terms, it may be necessary for us to file certain information about you with state or local government offices to protect our security interest in those products or to provide certain information about you to collection agencies in the event of non-payment or a payment dispute.

**What Choices Do You Have?**

Evine respects your right to make choices about the ways we collect, use and disclose your personal information. We generally ask you to indicate your choices at the time that you register as a user of EVINE.com or on the page where you provide your personal information. You may browse EVINE.com or Evine Mobile Applications without providing any information that identifies you personally and may choose not to provide the information we request, although this may mean that you cannot make a purchase or take advantage of other EVINE.com or Mobile Application features. When you register as an EVINE.com or Mobile Application user, you automatically start to receive information and product promotions periodically via e-mail. You may "opt-out" of receiving our promotional emails at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of the particular email. You may also manage your subscription and email preferences by clicking on "My Account" on EVINE.com, Evine’s Mobile Application or by sending us an email. To send us an email, please [click here](http://www.evine.com/p/help/email-us/).

**How Can You Update or Correct Your Personal Information?**

You may update your "account settings" information, including your name, contact information, credit card information, shipping and billing addresses, and subscription and email preferences at any time by clicking on "My Account" at EVINE.com. Instructions for updating your information are provided under "Account Settings." You can change your account settings at any time and as often as necessary. When you update your account settings, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records.

**Special Notice to California Residents**

We may share some of your information with third-party companies with whom we have contracts to provide products and services and/or with companies that use the information for their marketing purposes. The California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request information regarding to whom the business has disclosed personal information within the previous calendar year, along with the type of personal information disclosed to third-parties' direct marketing purposes. Please note that under this law, we are not required to respond to a customer's request more than once in a calendar year; furthermore we are only required to respond to requests sent to Evine-Privacy, 6740 Shady Oak Road, Eden Prairie, MN 55344.

**Security**

Evine has implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure with industry standard measures in place to protect the security of the personal information we collect through EVINE.com. For example, we use Transport Layer Security (“TSL”) to encrypt your credit card information as it travels over the Internet, and no credit card information is stored in EVINE’s infrastructure. It is important that you understand, however, that no website or database is completely secure or "hacker proof." You are also responsible for taking reasonable steps to protect your personal information against unauthorized disclosure or misuse, for example, by protecting your passwords. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our site. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for the circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the site.

**Links to Other Web Sites**

EVINE.com contains links to other websites operated by Evine and its corporate affiliates and service partners. It also contains links to websites that are owned and operated by unrelated third parties. This Online Privacy Statement applies only to personal information collected through EVINE.com. It does not apply to personal information collected on any other website operated by Evine or its corporate affiliates, nor to any website operated by any third party. These Web sites have their own policies regarding privacy. We recommend you review the privacy policy posted on any site you visit before using the site or providing any personal information about yourself.

**Children and Minors**

EVINE.com is not directed at nor targeted to children. We do not use this site to knowingly solicit personal information from or market to children. If you are under 13 years of age, you should not submit any personal information to us.
